Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
-Celal Kün.
-You where born in 1987, in Maraş. (Commercial AD)
Kahramanmaraş. (Kahraman=Hero, the word
was added after the war of independence)
-His profession?
-Senior master sergeant. I was in the special forces.
-Can you tell us about that day?
-It was the saddest day of my life. I didn't know.
It could've been the happiest. I thought
that I was at the doors of heaven.
I wanted to get in.
But it was hell.
Maraşlı will be on ATV in
11 January, Monday. (END of Commercial AD)
No harm was done to any creature during
the filming of this series.
May Allah bless your decision, daughter.
And may Allah keep you on this path.
Firstly, you need to recite the kalima
shahadah. Repeat after me.
I bear witness that...
...there is no god but Allah...
-there is no god but Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the servant of Allah.
Am I a Muslim now?
You are in a word, daughter. But a Muslim
is the one who is trusted by everyone.
The heart of a Muslim is the home of
trust, not treachery, daughter.
Don't betray those who believe in you.
You gave me shelter, you opened
your arms to me...
...how can I betray you?
-Don't, daughter. Don't.
Don't be a Muslim only by word.
Be a Muslim by your actions as well.
Thank you, Selcan Hatun.
-If you allow me...
-Of course, daughter. May Allah guide you.
Targun Hatun!
-What's wrong, Bala Hatun?
-I see that you learned to say Inshallah.
I'm a Muslim now.
Are you really?
-Or are you playing some games?
-What games, Bala Hatun?
-Don't you still trust me?
-Why did you hear or see to decide that?
Osman Bey's words and actions
fascinated me.
-I realized that his faith made him such--
-From now!
You'll never speak of Osman Bey's name!
Know that I'm watching you.
I won't take him out of my words
nor of my heart...
...but you will step away, Bala.
Have you finished the job
I've given you?
-Flatyos ran away, sir.
-You'll get your reward in Christ's heaven.
I'm not serving the pope
for Christ's heaven...
...but to send the Turks to hell, sir.
Sir, they are coming.
It's time.
Brother, we should be on our way.
We must find Flatyos.
If we can't find that dog,
we can't answer Osman Bey!
What is it that you can't answer, Göktuğ?
Flatyos ran away, Dündar Bey.
It has only been a
few days but...
...now you lost a man?
It seems that your bey made a mistake
by giving you this mission.
-Someone helped him, Dündar Bey.
-Even if so, it's your responsibility.
It's your fault.
What is it?
He ran away with this. Someone gave
this to him at night!
Come on, alps. We'll find that dog.
Come on!
From Oghuz Khagan to his sons...
...three bows and three arrows
were left.
His sons conquered the world
with those bows and arrows.
They founded great states.
With those states,
they brought justice to the realm...
...and spreaded the laws.
Now, whoever has the blessing of Allah,
who has the light of the laws...
...he is the great Turkish khagan...
...and others are his subjects.
When the Seljuk sultan bowed down
to the Mongols at Kösedağ...
...the great Turkish khaganete
tore down, the order went to lose.
The unity was broken. Turkish
tribes spread all over the world.
Osman Bey, it's the time of
bringing the order back...
...and uniting the tribes.
'Welcome, Bala Hatun'
Thank you, women.
Sit, please.
From now, you are the head hatun
of the tribe.
Come on, we are all listening to you.
Women. Every new bey comes with
his own methods and manners.
As the wife of Osman Bey, so have I.
As the time comes, I'll tell you how I
work and what I expect from you.
But, firstly, I want you to know
and don't forget...
...that Osman Bey doesn't only need
ghazis but also scholars now.
I'll bring teachers to teach how
to read.
'May Allah bless you'
Thank you.
I want you to make sure that your
children benefit from those teachers.
Thank you.
I have to do this.
I have to.
Osman Bey, you are looking
at those documents now.
How to kick the Mongols
out of these lands...
...how the order will be rebuilt when
the Anatolia becomes Turkish again...
...and how the unity will be assured,
are written in it.
Osman Bey, now the duty is yours and
your children's.
Bamsı Bey, now...
...we have the escrows.
I'll protect them at the
risk of my life.
I'll struggle for my state to be
a world power...
...for the Turkish khaganate...
...to be formed again.
Until...
...the sun of the laws can shine again,
unity can be formed again...
The three bows and three arrows
will come together again.
Long live Osman Bey!
This is what your grandfather Süleyman
Shah and your father Ertuğrul expects!
Come on, come on, Osman Bey!
Now return and start to build order.
Thank you, Bamsı Bey.
Oh my Allah, you destined
such a leader to the Turks...
...thank you.
Thank you...
Come on, women.
Let us drink our sherbet
and do our prayers.
Enjoy it.
-Osman is going. Should we follow him?
-We'll follow Osman a lot.
We must find the hole he is
hiding, and get the plans.
There will be a single man
in front of you...
...if you underestimate him,
none of you will survive.
Be cautious.
We'll kill Bamsı, get the plans...
...and leave here at once.
My dear friend Flatyos!
It's so nice to see you here.
So, your visit to the Kayı tribe
is over.
Good. Come, tell me.
What did you see,
what did you hear...
-Did you save me, Nikola?
-I would do it but I got help.
-From whom?
-Old Roman bishop.
Holy, mighty, respectable pope, we
can name him. An unexpected ally.
-I think it's something like the god's hand.
-The Pope in the Kayı Tribe...
I must admit that they are very good
at their work, Flatyos.
They have a man in everywhere.
Now the war starts again, my dear friend.
Osman became the bey, Nikola.
He united the tribes. They are more now.
He controls all the alps,
he is with Yavlak Arslan.
I know, Flatyos.
I know. Stop talking about Osman.
Look, we took a man from his tribe
on the first day of his reign.
-They were about to take my head.
-But have they?
They couldn't. So, don't be sad anymore.
We are stronger than before now, Flatyos.
We'll hurt more now.
And since Osman has the whole
responsibility of the tribe now...
...when we hurt someone,
we'll be hurting Osman.
Just like that, Flatyos.
Just like that.
We'll hurt more than before. And you
know me, I like to hurt.
Flatyos, maybe you should change
your shoes.
My Bey, we sent the alps everywhere.
But we couldn't find Flatyos.
That dog should've paid for
his crimes!
From the first day, how can you
make such a mistake?
What will we do?
Will we doubt you when we go out
to take care of something?
What are you saying, my bey? Don't you
know? We rather die than disobey you.
What is this, then?
You couldn't keep a single man!
Not only a man. Our archenemy who
killed our alps, Osman Bey.
My nephew brought the man in chains
and you lost him. Tell me, Osman Bey!
Get out.
Osman Bey!
Bala?
Bala...
Osman...
Bala!
Bala! Bala!
Bala, are you all right?
Open your eyes.
Bala, open your eyes!
Open your eyes. What's wrong?
Bala, Bala!
Bala!
-Osman!
-Aunt! Come, aunt!
Bala, daughter! Breath!
Leave us, go!
Aunt, aunt!
What did she eat?
Osman, she hardly breaths!
What will we do?
-Bala!
-Poison...
Open your eyes, Bala...
-Bala!
-Osman Bey!
I heard about Bala Hatun and I ran here.
I know about these things. I might help.
Come on, be quick. Come on!
Come on!
Her uvula is swelled out.
-I know the cure. I'll prepare the mix.
-Be quick.
Osman, Osman!
Are you sure to trust that girl now?
Here!
It must be close.
We are starting.
Be aware.
The hands that reach to the escrows,
get chopped, chopped, chopped!
Escrows are my honor!
These eyes saw the secret place!
They haven't!
There are no eyes!
You came to your death!
No, we came to your funeral, Bamsı Bey!
Bala, open your mouth.
Help us, my Allah.
Selcan Hatun, help me.
You are the mightiest, my Allah!
Now, we will wait.
My love...
Help her, my Allah...
You can't reach to the escrows
that Bamsı protects! You can't
O' Bamsı the Big.
It's your turn now.
Look, Ertuğrul Bey is gone too.
And Bamsı...
...Hafsa awaits you.
Your children await.
Your prophet awaits.
You should give your life now.
My Allah, thank you.
For making me a martyr.
My Allah, make
me a neighbor...
...to our prophet.
Amin.
It's my turn now.
I protected the escrows, my bey.
I protected the escrows.
-Bala, Bala!
-Osman...
Thank Allah, thank Allah!
Thank Allah...
Thank Allah she came round.
Aygül, Gonca...
...put Targun Hatun to
cage tent.
Osman Bey, what--
You are making a mistake!
Osman Bey!
It's over, daughter.
It's over.
We'll kill him and get the escrows.
Come, come...
...come to the hell you are
looking for.
Look who is here!
We are here, Bamsı Bey!
Osman didn't leave his man alone!
Valiants, victory belongs
to those who have faith!
Ya Allah!
I always liked you, Bamsı Bey.
Now, I'm starting to like you, Cerkutay!
Bamsı Bey!
Abdurrahman Ghazi!
God damn you, Osman!
So, Abdurrahman Ghazi,
just like the old days, huh?
Yes, brother.
With a single arm, we are
enough for all of them, Bamsı.
Thank Allah, thank Allah, brother.
Lads, there is a cover there.
You'll find two chests. Bring them here.
All right, my bey.
My bey, what were you doing
here alone?
Cerkutay, alps don't ask questions.
What are in the chests, my bey?
Cerkutay.
So, Abdurrahman Ghaz, tell me.
Where did you come from?
-Osman Bey sent us, brother. Osman Bey.
-Oh, Osman Bey...
...mashallah to him.
He wanted me to come.
Cerkutay, I'm glad you came.
Without you, how would've we be like?
I'm glad you did, Cerkutay.
Alps, we need to take these chests
to Osman Bey at once.
Cerkutay, come with us.
Come with us, Cerkutay.
Come on, come one.
-What will we do now?
-We'll follow them.
Bala.
-Are you better now?
-I'm fine, Osman.
I'm better now.
Why are your eyes wet?
-You are the bey now.
-You are the bey's wife now.
Your wife lays here, Osman Bey.
Where is your heir?
I pray for a child.
I wish it to be my child,
not another woman's.
So do I, Bala.
So do I.
I want you to give me a heir.
I want my children to carry
your noble soul.
I want to see the jihad love of Kayı beys,
and your pure heart on them.
You want your blood to continue
through me.
But, if Allah hasn't destine it...
...it will go through someone else, Osman.
I pray, Bala.
I ask it from Allah.
I await.
-What else can we do?
-You await, Osman Bey.
But the enemy doesn't.
Look what they've done to me.
I'll make them pay for this.
I'll make them pay.
Don't worry, Bala.
You need an heir, Osman.
Until that heir borns...
...neither you nor me will
be free of these troubles.
Neither you nor our tribe
will have a future.
Would Targun try this if you had
an heir?
Bala...
...Bala...
Don't think about these.
Think about our love.
Think about our love and smile.
Come on.
Come on, smile.
Bring the sun to my tent with your smile.
Just like that.
My heart is already warm.
Recover as soon as you can.
All the Kayı women await you.
They are worried about you.
May I enter, my bey.
Come.
-Come, Master Davud.
-We have news from Saltuk, my bey.
Dündar Bey...
What did Dündar Bey do?
He left the tents to meet
with Nikola.
-What did he do?
-Saltık sent word before leaving.
He'll meet with Nikola's men
and they will go to the meeting point.
Dündar Bey, Süleyman Shah's son.
Went to the heathen, is that so?
He still dreams of being a bey.
Uncle...
What else do you want?
What are you after?
What are you forcing me into?
My bey, what will we do
if Osman Bey hears this?
He will not hear it, Saltuk.
He will not hear it.
Dündar Bey, we live in strange times.
It's getting harder to find someone smart.
Do you see yourself as a smart man?
No, no, I'm a man who can act weird
and do unexpected things.
Like Osman, I'm a bit crazy.
When there are no smart people between
two crazy people...
...the innocent people pay for it.
-What do you want from me, Nikola?
-What I want is known, Dündar Bey.
I want Kulucahisar. And you want to
be a bey, don't you?
We'll take the title from Osman
and give it to you.
Don't make your decision right away,
Dündar Bey. Think about it.
You ask me to betray my own tribe.
Dündar Bey.
If I were you, I would never
call it treason.
Think about it, you are the bey,
you sit on the fur.
And as soon as you sit...
...both Rome and the Mongols
attacks.
-And you want me to give you Kulucahisar?
-As a sign of our friendship.
We are in times that we need to remember
that peace is a virtue, Dündar Bey.
Rome made agreements with everyone.
Why wouldn't it make agreements
with the Turks?
But because of the kinds of Osman...
Open the door.
I never trusted you.
I didn't do anything.
On the contrary...
...I saved Bala.
You first poisoned her,
then saved her.
Is that so?
How do I know that you didn't?
Is it a lie that your mother tried
to poison all the Kayı beys?
Don't talk about my mother!
You want Bala to die...
...because you also love Osman.
Confess it.
Will you kill someone tied?
Kill me! Come on!
If I wasn't going to answer Osman Bey...
...I would cut your tongue here.
I pity you, Aygül.
I pity you for leaving your love
to someone else.
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Now, you will answer to Osman Bey!
Move now! Move, I said!
Move! Move!
-Can I enter, my bey?
-Come, Aygül.
Even if I forgive you,
the laws won't.
Targun Hatun.
Don't waste my time and
accept your crime.
I'm not guilty.
Why should I accept it.
You said that you'll be a Muslim.
Does a Muslim lie?
Did you believe it?
I wanted to believe.
I loved you, Osman Bey.
I wanted you to like me.
I wanted you to marry me.
Did you convert even though
you didn't believe?
Aren't you afraid of committing a sin?
I'm not afraid to burn in hell for you.
You'll die in hell for me, huh?
But I live in heaven.
I live with angel.
Who sealed my heart,
who tied my hands...
Who imprisoned me in her eyes...
I wish I spared some of that poison...
...and didn't run here with the
cure like an idiot.
If you weren't a woman,
I would kill you here.
Because of the things you had
done to me and my wife...
...and for your false conversion,
I banish you!
You and your father will never
come to these tents.
And you, Göktuğ.
You failed me.
You couldn't guard my enemy.
I don't want to see you either.
You won't come to these tents.
You are spurring all the things my brother
and I did, for a single mistake.
That's what one would expect from a
bey who banish the woman...
...who says that she would burn.
in hell for him.
You have never been worthy
of your brother.
Get out of my face!
You will not come to these tents again!
Go!
So, she won't come to these tents
again. Is that so, Osman Bey?
-It's true.
-Is that the punishment of killing your wife?
Releasing her? Would you be so
merciful to someone else?
Are you jealous of her, Bala?
Can't I have some other
reason for that?
Tell me too, then.
Including you, everyone will
know things...
...but...
...only I will know everything.
Is that so, Osman Bey?
Yes.
-What's wrong, Boran Alp?
-Nothing, Dündar Bey.
Dündar Bey, Osman Bey wants you
in his tent.
What's wrong, Dündar Bey?
Had something happen?
Either my death order or my
salvation.
What are you saying, Dündar Bey?
What death?
Who can kill you?
If you think things are going bad,
send word to Yavlak Arslan to save me.
What did you do, Dündar Bey?
Stay calm, woman. I'll figure something
out. Stay calm.
Come on. Go.
What did you do to us, Dündar Bey?
Uncle.
Brother of my uncle.
-Do you know why I called you?
-I know, Osman Bey. I know.
So, you know.
You wonder where I was.
Boran, take my uncle's weapons.
Come, uncle.
Come.
Where were you?
-Where were you, uncle?
-I went to Nikola, nephew.
Why did you do that?
He wants your head. He offers
co-operation.
Is that so?
Yes.
And, what did you say?
What did you say?
For him to not get suspicious,
I got mad and shouted first.
''Do you think I'm a traitor?'' I said.
But then I acted like I was convinced.
He spoke and I listened.
I didn't say anything certain but...
...but he thinks that I'm trapped.
Uncle...
Is that so?
So, you say that.
-Yes.
-But...
It looks like you are trapped, uncle.
Why did you do that?
For you to trap him when you want.
If I had invited him, he would
get suspicious.
But he invited me.
Now, he wants to use
me against you.
But, you should use me against him,
nephew.
Those who come from
the bey's family...
...shouldn't get bleed...
...here...
...for this reason...
...if...
...they betray...
...then, they...
...get strangled...
...with bow string.
Uncle!
Without asking me...
...how can you act on your own?
How can you step over the bey?
Wasn't it you who said that
there is a traitor in the tents?
If I had come and told you,
they would tell it to Nikola.
But, I wanted to be seen like
I was acting on my own.
Don't worry, uncle. There won't be
any traitor left in the tents.
I will kill them all. All of them.
Everyone who schemes from my back
will end badly.
Those who don't want the same fate,
will act accordingly.
My bey, Bamsı Bey is here.
He is wounded.
And from now...
...even if it's for me,
nothing will be done...
...without my information.
It shall be known.
The heathens, the heathens
attacked me, Osman Bey.
But, there is nothing
to concern.
You say so, huh?
But I don't think so, Bamsı Bey.
Not really.
Be careful.
Long you live, Osman Bey!
Don't worry about the escrows.
Abdurrahman Ghazi will hide them
in somewhere safe.
We don't have time to lose.
We must invite the beys to meeting.
Send word to frontiersmen. I'll talk to
them about something important in Söğüt.
-As you order, my bey.
-Thank you, lad.
Bamsı Bey.
So, they followed us, huh?
If they haven't known where
we were going...
...they wouldn't follow us...
...but where did they learn it?
I can't understand.
They don't know where we went,
but why we went.
That's why they followed, Bamsı Bey.
That's how they learned.
How did they hear of the secret that only
Ertuğrul Bey and I knew?
Bamsı Bey, they are...
...are like our old enemies...
...my father's enemies.
They are stronger enemies than
heathen Nikola.
Stronger, you say, huh?
So it seems.
The escrows are in danger, Bamsı Bey.
Everyone is in danger, Bamsı Bey.
We must hurry. The circle narrows.
My father would want me to work
with my brothers.
That's what I'll do.
I'll do...
...and we'll stand strong.
-You are right, Osman Bey.
That's what your father would
want.
Osman Bey.
There is something else that
is important.
What is it, Osman Bey?
Osman Bey went to Bamsı's tent.
He'll tell Osman about the incident.
What we were looking for was
in those chests.
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
If it wasn't for you, I wouldn't
be able to sell all these.
Abdurrahman Ghazi is missing.
No, mister, no! Instead of selling it
to you at that price, I rather smash it!
Have some mercy!
All right, all right. Have it your way.
He is a good trader.
This man named Abdurrahman.
Keep your eyes on him all the time.
We'll go and talk to this Osman.
Open it, lad.
Bamsı Bey.
-It's my father's will.
-It is.
-He says that he choose me to be the bey.
-Of course, Osman Bey.
Tells me to give duties
to my brother and uncle.
To keep their hearts warm.
He is right, Osman Bey.
He is right.
Bamsı Bey.
Why didn't you tell me before.
He told Abdurrahman Ghazi to keep it
until the end of the elections.
Osman Bey.
Have you read it until the end?
My father tells me to find a new wife.
He orders me.
He is right, Osman Bey.
He is right, son.
Now, as long as you don't
have an heir...
...your reign is in danger.
Solve this.
Osman Bey...
Son...
You both will grin and bear it.
You will bow down to the decision
of god.
Osman Bey, you will do as the will says.
Osman Bey, will he come?
He will.
-What's your job?
-We are traders.
-Where are your goods?
-In Söğüt.
Söğüt?
Why did you laugh?
If it wasn't for Bamsı Bey, I would have
burned Söğüt.
When we heard that you became the bey,
we ran here. We wanted to congratulate.
Thank you, thank you.
I wanted to talk to you.
I want you to do more than
trading goods.
What can the Kayıs sell to whom?
Other than what we already do.
What can they buy from where?
Tell me.
We accept that as an order, my bey.
From Damascus to Ankara...
...we know all the markets.
We can sell all the goods of the Kayı
in the markets...
...just ask it, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
But the first condition of trade
is that nothing is free, Osman Bey.
What kind of a bey makes his helpers
regret?
Forgive us if he offended you, my bey.
He went over his level.
Every job has different customs and
language.
Do your trade.
And we'll do our job.
Of course.
Then, give us a store in Söğüt.
Give us so that we can expand
our trade, my bey.
All right.
Boran Alp, give them a store in Söğüt.
And provide them everything they need.
As you order, my bey.
-May Allah give you luck in your trade.
-Amin.
Such a beadledom could only come
from a trader.
Osman will think that.
-What did he do?
-Give me water, woman.
Give me water, come on.
You put bowstring to my neck, huh?
Do you threaten me with death?
What did he do?
Did he attempt to kill you?
It leads to that.
He hold grudge against me.
He looks for a mistake of mine.
What will we do, then?
What will we do?
Should we leave here?
What should we do?
This is my father's tribe!
My father's tribe!
I was here before them!
I was here!
I will stay and they will leave!
You put a bowstring to my neck, huh?
That Savcı and Gündüz
watched their uncle dying.
Osman...
None of them are our friends.
None of them wants us here.
Didn't I tell you, Dündar Bey?
So, what will we do now?
How will we get out of this situation?
I will ask for forgiveness.
I will ask for forgiveness from my nephew.
Dündar Bey.
You were like a hungry wolf
a moment ago.
What's wrong? Happened that you
turned into a sheep?
Woman.
From now.
I'll be a wolf under a sheep's disguise.
A sheep in the tribe, a wolf outside.
Firstly, I'll gain Osman's trust.
Then, I'll whip that bowstring...
...around his neck.
Around his neck.
You'll be on good terms with Bala.
You won't argue with Selcan.
For a while, play this game. Make them
think that they have us.
They should tend to their business
and forget about us.
When they expect the least.
We'll come back again.
Again.
We invited and
you honored us.
Thank you all.
May Allah never takes you from us.
-Amin.
Of course, we'll come, my nephew.
From now, you are our bey.
Even though I'm older, I should
act accordingly to your word.
I made a mistake.
From now, it's your place to forgive.
Will you forgive me?
That's why I wanted this dinner.
To end the fights and rivalries
end between us.
Everyone should know their place
and their age.
From now, everyone should treat
each other accordingly.
Uncle, if you ask for forgiveness.
If you say that it won't happen again.
Then, I'll forgive you, uncle.
From now, we should come together
in such nights.
Share our breads.
We should share so that we can
remember that...
...we are relatives,
that we carry the same blood.
Tell me, mother. Is it appropriate for
us to be estranged from each other?
Of course not.
Of course not, son.
Every encounter is an opportunity
for penitence.
Every unification...
...is the door of starting again.
You spoke well, aunt.
Many times, when I was performing
ablution, I thought the same.
I tell myself, you freshened your intentions,
don't break yours before the other does.
You are right, brother.
I wish we can hold ours, even if the others
breaks theirs.
Gündüz Bey.
This is a word worthy of sufistics.
My nephew has the heart of a fakir.
Even if one wants to fight,
it can't be against him.
His heart is so pure that, whatever
he says is true.
Thank you, uncle.
We, women, should take our
lessons from these words.
It's life, we might break each other...
...but we should have the dignity
left to look at each other in the face.
Of course...
Of course, Bala Hatun.
Back in the time, we would get along
so well.
Let us be like that again.
Inshallah.
The tongue has no bones.
And bad memories can't get forgotten
easily.
But, we shouldn't get to the point that
we can't look each other in the face.
Mashallah to our pretty khatun.
Mashallah.
This peace should take as long
as it can.
In my part, I won't be the one
who breaks it.
If someone takes a step for me,
I'll take two for them.
No one should doubt it.
As long as it's sincere.
Thank you.
So, my nephew Bayhoca.
Say a few words.
How is the situation in Konya?
How are the madrasahs? Tell us.
Nothing can grow in the soil
that Mongols step on, uncle.
Science gets its share from that.
Do you say that scholars are dispersing?
Yes, uncle. But not to east,
they are going to west.
-Are they going to the borders?
-To the borders.
Brother. What should we do to
convince those scholars.
Scholars need madrasahs, Osman Bey.
Madrasahs need a city.
A city needs a state.
It needs a state.
Come on.
With the name of Allah.
Go on.
Enjoy your meal.
I informed the frontiersmen.
-Tomorrow, they'll come to Söğüt.
-May it be good, Osman Bey.
Do you wish to celebrate your title?
We already finished that, uncle.
From now, I want to conquer
İnegöl Castle.
With the name of Allah.
Cerkutay is coming.
Come, Cerkutay.
Come.
'May I come?', you should say, Cerkutay.
May I come?
Cerkutay.
Come here.
Don't you have a mother, father...
or any brothers?
They're dead.
Did you spend all your life in wars?
Don't you have a lover?
A warrior's lover is his gun, right?
Cerkutay...
Yes.
A warrior's lover is his gun.
However...
Cerkutay...
love is necessary.
Someone other than you.
Loving someone more than yourself is hard.
I'd love to...
love someone else...
more than myself...
I'd love that.
You're young, Cerkutay.
You're young.
You will love.
You will be loved.
You'll understand how good it is.
My Bey, you shouldn't fight anymore.
Why?
My whole family is dead.
I don't want you to die.
Cerkutay...
You've just burned my heart.
Cerkutay, I have more years.
I'll raise you.
Listen to me well.
I was my Ertuğrul Bey's Bamsı.
Now, you...
will be Osman Bey's Bamsı.
You'll be Osman Bey's Bamsı.
Will I have a beard like yours?
Oh, Cerkutay.
You made me smile, may Allah
make you smile too.
I'm ready, my Bey.
Tell me everything.
Will you ask for support from Beys
to conquer İnegöl, Osman Bey?
Yes, brother.
But...
İnegöl Castle is hard to conquer.
It's tough.
Firstly...
I want to see the preparations.
Thank you.
You do everything right.
What if they don't support?
The Beys are valiants who
fought next to my father.
We'll convince them.
- What if they don't support us anyway?
- We'll tell them...
the importance of the situation
and the idea of war.
We have to be together
for freedom and justice.
If needed...
we'll go to...
Germiyanids ourselves.
It's my father's will...
and...
my will.
Brother...
I want something from you.
Yes, brother.
I want you to meet Nikola in a safe place.
Tell him that I want peace.
- Will he believe me?
- He'll want to believe you, uncle.
We killed his soldiers last time.
He won't be able to fight without a
support.
Why do we want peace?
I want to stop him until I reach my goal.
He'll think he's wasting our time.
However...
we'll be digging his grave.
Don't worry.
I'll meet him.
Are there any duties for me?
Osman Bey's duties are dangerous, Bayhoca.
Firstly...
ask for permission from your
mother and father.
Ask me later.
Is it all done?
Yes, my Bey.
These goods are the last ones.
This place will be opened tomorrow.
We promised to Osman Bey.
Thank you, valiants.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Is the news you'll tell me...
about the feast in Söğüt?
So you know.
I have ears.
I can hear too.
Then...
you may know Osman is taking action.
I've heard that he'll gather all the Beys
in Söğüt.
Then, you know.
- You know why.
- It's obvious why.
He'll gather all of the Uç Beys.
He'll attack İnegöl with a big army.
It's Osman.
He'll do it.
Stop acting as if you're not afraid.
If he succeeds, he won't just
conquer İnegöl...
you know what comes next...
- after İnegöl.
- What are you thinking?
Beys won't come to Söğüt tomorrow...
their corpses will.
All of them?
Yes.
We should frighten Osman.
We shouldn't let him sleep comfortably.
He should see
the corpses in his nightmares.
Look, son.
Next to there belongs to Kayıs.
- Our Ertuğrul Bey's lands.
- We should go to Ertuğrul Bey's grave.
Yes, we should.
- Have you ever seen Osman Bey, father?
- Yes.
He was young at that time.
Ertuğrul Bey took him with himself
when he was coming to our tent.
It was obvious that he'd be a good Bey.
Why does he want us in Söğüt?
Osman Bey wants to do what his father did.
That's why he has invited us.
That' what we'll do.
Now.
Father!
Father!;
Father! Father!
Father!
Okay.
Enough.
Father!
The child will bring his father's corpse
to Söğüt.
Osman Bey will see that we are peaceful.
Osman Bey is coming!
Long live Osman Bey!
Thank you!
May it be easy.
May it be fruitful.
- Welcome, my Bey.
- Thank you.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
- I congratulate you for being the new Bey.
Thank you.
Mashallah to you.
- Take it.
- Thank you, Osman Bey.
- Thank you. Enjoy it.
Come on.
Welcome, my Bey. May Allah
give you a long life.
- Amin.
- You came with your goodness.
- May your Beyhood will be good.
Thank you.
- Welcome, my Bey.
- Welcome, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Mashallah.
- It suits you.
- Thank you.
Thank you. May Allah give you a long life.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Welcome.
Our Beylic will grow. Inshaallah...
our trade will grow.
We'll establish new bazaars.
We'll take our goods to
places we can't reach now.
You're right, My Bey but
it requires a big preparation.
The craftsmen and the merchants should
be prepared.
Yes.
You're right.
What do you sell?
I sell honey, butter and tallow.
Here.
Mashallah.
- Thank you.
- May it be Halal.
- My brother is doing cereal trade.
How much goods...
- do you bring?
- I bring goods full of four cars.
And with two horses full of goods.
What if...
you bring goods to Bursa?
To İznik? Konya?
Sivas?
I'll need countless cars and horses.
We'll need more men.
And production should be boosted.
To boost the production and...
to send the goods to everywhere...
I'll do everything I can.
We'll make inconvenient
people stronger together.
So that our people will fight.
They will be strong.
What I should do is...
to make the people stronger.
I'll meet with merchants in a short time
and discuss the problem.
Thank you, my Bey.
Osman Bey.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
I congratulate your Beyhood, Osman Bey.
I tried to come as soon as possible.
Thank you.
Are you ready?
The whole Kastamonu is waiting.
We're waiting for Geyhatu to come
back from Tabriz.
We are ready for anything with the
help of Allah.
We have one thing
to do before Geyhatu comes back.
I'll have all the power of Uç Beys and...
conquer İnegöl.
We should be sure of them...
so that we can be powerful when
Geyhatu comes back.
You should have your Alps and Uç Beys.
Then we'll do what we should do.
Thank you.
So, you did it.
Congratulations.
Thanks to you, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
We'll make so many good things together
with the blessing of your Beyhood.
You...
take care of what I said.
I'm waiting for
your information about new bazaars.
Don't worry, my Bey.
May it be easy.
Why aren't the Beys here?
They killed my father!
- Father!
- It's Hasan Bey's son.
Hasan Bey?
They killed my father!
Take my father's revenge, Osman Bey.
He was going to fight for you.
Wait, Osman.
It's just a beginning.
Don't...
worry.
Father!
My Bey.
They killed three Beys.
Fazlı Bey, İlyas Bey and Turan Bey.
So, they knew it.
They knew who would come.
What's written on that paper, Gündüz Bey?
It's just a beginning.
Until all of the Turks die.
From now on...
I'll breathe death...
and cause distress!
If anyone is...
included in this...
I'll...
rip their lungs off...
and make the dogs eat them!
If I don't take their revenge...
then...
I'm not the son of Ertuğrul Ghazi...
Osman Bey.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com